jerktastic.com 2010-12-31

# Jerktastic - Jerktastic

## **Privacy Policy**

The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy.  
This Privacy Policy describes how Jerktastic.com collects information from all end-users and what we do with the information we collect, and the choices visitors and members have concerning the collection and use of such information.  
Jerktastic.com encourages you to read this privacy policy carefully and those of all websites you visit. 

**Revisions to this Policy**

Jerktastic.com reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. The user should periodically check for any modifications of this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on the user`s browser. The user should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the "last modified" date remains unchanged after the user has clicked the "refresh" button on his/her browser, the user may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the policy. A changed "last modified" dates indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting. 

**Personal Information**

**A.** \- Jerktastic.com collects information in different ways from visitors and members who access the various parts of our website. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our website and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected when we believe that such disclosure is required by law.  
 **B.** \- Jerktastic.com also collects IP addresses, referral URLs, browser preferences. This information is used internally to track how users come to be referred to our sites for the purpose of compensating our affiliates, advertisers, and other marketing entities. This information may be disclosed to third-parties. If we choose to disclose information to third-parties, this information shall consist of non-specific information regarding site traffic and statistics. Jerktastic.com never discloses any customer-specific information to third parties unless it is reasonable to believe that doing so is required by law, a binding contract, a Court Order, or other state, local, or administrative regulation.   
**C.** \- It is Jerktastic`s policy not to use or share the personal information about visitors or members in ways unrelated to those described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, Jerktastic.com may disclose personal information about visitors or members, or information regarding your use of the services or websites accessible through our website, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including:   
* To satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information;   
* To disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies;   
* To operate the Services properly;   
* To protect Jerktastic.com and our members;   
* We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include compliance with discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, and writs.   
**D.** \- Cookies - A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. Jerktastic.com may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve our website and services we provide. We may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services to you. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. 

**Our Commitment to Children`s Protection**

Our sites are designed for adults, but not for use by anyone under the age of 18. In light of that fact, the Children`s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 is not applicable to this site. We have no web pages designed for younger users. We make every effort to ensure that our websites contain adequate warnings to make their content obvious and to warn users under the age of 18 that they are not welcome to view our websites, we believe that there is no substitute for proper parental supervision of their children`s internet use. Nevertheless, we will take any steps possible to discourage those under the age of 18 from visiting our websites. For further information about tips, tools, age-appropriate, or kid-friendly websites and how to report online trouble, please visit www.getnetwise.org. 

**External Sites**

The website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our website they should read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Where to Direct Questions about Our Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at
